<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>/</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 14:36:44 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/webmasterish/vuepress-plugin-feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cadence Community Spotlight Update - March 2022]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2022/03/31/_31-community-spotlight-update-march-2022/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2022/03/31/_31-community-spotlight-update-march-2022/</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to our Cadence Community Spotlight update!

This is the latest in our series of monthly blog posts focused on the Cadence community and news about what you have been doing with Cadence.

Please see below for a short activity roundup of what has happened recently in the community.

Updated Cadence Topology Diagram

Did you know that we have an updated Cadence Service diagram on the website? Well we do - and you can find it on our Deployment Topology page. We are always looking for information that helps makes it easier for people to understand how Cadence works.

Special thanks to Ben Slater for updating the diagram and also to Ender, Emrah and Long for helping review it.

Monthly Cadence Technical Office Hours

Every month we hold a Technical Office Hours session via Zoom where you can speak directly with some of our Cadence experts. If you have a question about Cadence or are facing a particular issue getting ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cadence Community Spotlight Update - February 2022]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2022/02/28/community-spotlight-february-2022/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2022/02/28/community-spotlight-february-2022/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the Cadence Community Spotlight update!

This is the second in our series of monthly updates focused on the Cadence community and news about what you have been doing with Cadence. We hope that you enjoyed last month's update and are keen to find out what has been happening.

Please see below for a short activity roundup of what has happened recently in the community.

Announcements

Just in case you missed it the alpha version of the Cadence notification service has been released. Details can be found at the following link:
Cadence Notification Service

Thanks very much to everyone that worked on this!

Community Supporting the Community

During February 16 questions were posted in the Cadence #support Slack channel from new Cadence users and existing community members looking for help and guidance. A very big thank you to the following community members who to ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cadence Community Spotlight Update - January 2022]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2022/01/31/community-spotlight-january-2022/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2022/01/31/community-spotlight-january-2022/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to our very first Cadence Community Spotlight update!

This monthly update focuses on news from the wider Cadence community and is all about what you have been doing with Cadence. Do you have an interesting project that uses Cadence? If so then we want to hear from you. Also if you have any news items, blogs, articles, videos or events where Cadence has been mentioned then that is good too. We want to showcase that our community is active and is doing exciting and interesting things.

Please see below for a short round up of things that have happened recently in the community.

Community Related Office Hours

On the 12th January 2022 we held our first Cadence Community Related Office Hours. This session was focused on discussing how we plan and organise things for the community. This includes things such as Code of Conduct, managing social media and making sure we regularly communicate project news and events.

And you can see that this monthly update is the result of the fe ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moving to gRPC]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2021/10/19/moving-to-grpc/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2021/10/19/moving-to-grpc/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cadence historically has been using TChannel transport with Thrift encoding for both internal RPC calls and communication with client SDKs. gRPC is becoming a de-facto industry standard with much better adoption and community support. It offers features such as authentication and streaming that are very relevant for Cadence. Moreover, TChannel is being deprecated within Uber itself, pushing an effort for this migration. During the last year we’ve implemented multiple changes in server and SDK that allows users to use gRPC in Cadence, as well as to upgrade their existing Cadence cluster in a backward compatible way. This post tracks the completed work items and our future plans.

Our Approach
With ~500 services using Cadence at Uber and many more open source customers around the world, we had to think about the gRPC transition in a backwards compatible way. We couldn’t simply flip transport and encoding everywhere. Instead we needed to support both protocols as an intermediate step ...]]></description>
            <enclosure url="/img/grpc-migration.svg">
            </enclosure>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Announcing Cadence OSS office hours and community sync up]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2021/10/13/announcing-cadence-oss-office-hours-and-community-sync-up/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2021/10/13/announcing-cadence-oss-office-hours-and-community-sync-up/</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Are you a current Cadence user, do you operate Cadence services, or are you interested in learning about workflow technologies and wonder what problems Cadence could solve for you? We would like to talk to you!

Our team has spent a significant amount of time working with users and partner teams at Uber to design, scale and operate their workflows. This helps our users understand the technology better, smooth their learning curve and ramp up experience, and at the same time allows us to get fast and direct feedback so we can improve the developer experience and close feature gaps. As our product and community grows, we would like to expand this practice to our users in the OSS community. For the first time ever, members of the Cadence team along with core contributors from the community will host bi-weekly office hours to answer any questions you have about Cadence, or workflow technology in general. We can also dedicate future sessions to specific topics that have a common intere ...]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>