<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>/</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:27:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/webmasterish/vuepress-plugin-feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Cadence Community Survey Results]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2023/06/08/survey-results/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2023/06/08/survey-results/</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We released a user survey earlier this year to learn about who our users are, how they use Cadence, and how we can help them. It was shared from our Slack workspace, cadenceworkflow.io Blog and LinkedIn. After collecting the feedback, we wanted to share the results with our community. Thank you everyone for filling it out! Your feedback is invaluable and it helps us shape our roadmap for the future.

Here are some highlights in text and you can check out the visuals to get more details:

using.png

job_role.png

Most of the people who replied to our survey were engineers who were already using Cadence, actively evaluating, or migrating from a similar technology. This was exciting to hear! Some of you have contacted us to learn more about benchmarks, scale, and ideal ...]]></description>
            <enclosure url="/../../shared/img/2023-survey-results/using.png">
            </enclosure>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cadence Community Spotlight Update - March 2023]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2023/03/31/community-spotlight-march-2023/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2023/03/31/community-spotlight-march-2023/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the latest of our regular monthly Community Spotlight updates that gives you news from in and around the Cadence community!

Please see below for a roundup of the highlights:

Cadence at Open Source Summit, North America
We are very pleased to let you know that a talk on Cadence has been accepted for the Linux Foundation's Open Source Summit, North America in Vancouver on 10th - 12th May 2023.

The talk called Cadence: The New Open Source Project for Building Complex Distributed Applications will be given by Ender Demirkaya and Emrah Seker If you are planning to attend the Open Source Summit then please don't forget to attend the talk and take time catch up with Ender and Emrah!

Community Activity
Our Slack #support channel has been very active over the last fe ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cadence Community Spotlight Update - February 2023]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2023/02/28/community-spotlight-february/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2023/02/28/community-spotlight-february/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Here’s the latest in our regular monthly Community Spotlight updates that gives you news from in and around the Cadence community!

Please see below for a roundup of the highlights:

Community Survey
We've been talking about doing a community survey for a while and during February we sent it out. We are still collating the results so it's not too late to send in your response.

The survey takes 5 minutes and is your opportunity to provide feedback to the project and highlight areas you think we need to focus on.

Use this Survey Link

Please take a few minutes to give us your opinion.

Cadence and Temporal
During user surveys we've had a few queries about whether Cadence and Temporal are the same project. The answer is No - they are not the same project but they do share the same origin. At a high level Temporal is a fork of the Cadence project. Both Temporal and Cadence are now being developed by different ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cadence Community Spotlight Update - January 2023]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2023/01/31/community-spotlight-january-2023/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2023/01/31/community-spotlight-january-2023/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Happy New Year everyone! Here’s the latest in our regular monthly Community Spotlight updates that gives you news from in and around the Cadence community!

Please see below for a roundup of the highlights:

Closing Down Cadence Office Hours
We have been running Office Hours sessions every month since May last year. The aim was to give the community an opportunity to speak directly with some of the Cadence core developers and experts to answer questions on particular issues you may be having. We have found that the most preferred method for community questions has been the support Slack channel so have decided to stop this monthly call.

Thanks very much to Ender Demirkayaand the Uber team for making themselves available for these sessions.

Please remember that if you have question about Cadence or are facing a specific issue then  you can post your question in our #support Slack channel. If you al ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cadence Community Spotlight Update - December 2022]]></title>
            <link>/blog/2022/12/23/community-spotlight-december-2022/</link>
            <guid>/blog/2022/12/23/community-spotlight-december-2022/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[I know we are a little early this month as many people will be taking some time out for holidays.

Happy Holidays

We'd like to wish everyone happy holidays and to thank you for being part of the Cadence community. It's been a busy year for Cadence as we have continued to build a strong, active community that works together to solve issues and generally support each other.

Let's keep going!...This is a great way to build a sustainable community.

We are sure that 2023 will be even more exciting as we continue to develop Cadence.

Cadence in the News!

Below are a selection of Cadence related articles, blogs and whitepapers. Please take a look and feel free to share via your own social media channels.

Cadence iWF

Child Workflow Cookbook

[Cadence Connection Examples Using TLS](https://www.instaclus ...]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>